Jane Swanson: of this… Project?
Rachel Liu: Robbie, do you want to take that?
Robbie Dornbush: Yeah, absolutely. So, the goal for both of us is, as part of our studio curriculum, we are working to develop a solution set or product to take on the questions that Rachel touched on at the top. Right now, we are interviewing subject matter experts.
Robbie Dornbush: who have, experience, either direct or as part of their work, with the issues that we're dealing with, and we're going to take a lot of that research and that input to shape the products that we're developing. So right now, we're really in an exploratory phase, really trying to better understand the questions that drive our products.
Robbie Dornbush: Before we begin developing them. So the goal of this is to, further hone our understanding of the problems that we're taking on.
Jane Swanson: Thank you, that's helpful.
Rachel Liu: Cool. Should we jump right in?
Robbie Dornbush: Yeah, absolutely.
Rachel Liu: Okay, perfect. I'll start us off with kind of, like, a very open-ended question, which is, kind of what is…
Rachel Liu: as you understand it, that step-by-step process for, kind of… or just, like, your experience with engaging with, I believe, like, students within Cornell Tech when it comes to civic engagement, and then how you
Rachel Liu: Would define your relationship with the local government as well, in, in that kind of relationship.
Jane Swanson: Local government, just, or also, organizations.
Rachel Liu: Yeah, sure, I mean, everything.
Jane Swanson: She's on…
Robbie Dornbush: Yeah.
Jane Swanson: When we're talking…
Jane Swanson: I mean, Roosevelt Island I can talk about in general, maybe a few other places, but okay to focus on Roosevelt Island for now.
Robbie Dornbush: Yeah.
Jane Swanson: Yeah. With regard to student engagement, and are we… would you like to hear about student engagement.
Jane Swanson: on Roosevelt Island with our community, you know, that type of thing, how we make that happen.
Rachel Liu: That would be helpful, and then something else that would also be nice is if you could share a little bit about if there's, like.
Rachel Liu: tools in which you're using to track all of this information, maybe how you're tracking, like, engagement or metrics that you use to measure, you know, what you would call success. That would also be helpful as well from the data side.
Jane Swanson: We could really use help with that a little bit.
Jane Swanson: So, just to start off, at the beginning, as you probably know, at the beginning of the academic year.
Jane Swanson: The clubs are formed, and there is a community, Service Club.
Jane Swanson: that's formed. I think it's… we've been… the club has formed over the last 2 years.
Jane Swanson: And there are actually, although the clubs are master's students, in this case, the clubs have been
Jane Swanson: generated a little bit, or helped along through two PhD students who are here. So, I guess the first thing I can say is it sort of helps to have students
Jane Swanson: Who are here more than a year, and obviously, you know, for the engagement, and the,
Jane Swanson: the PhD students, you know, are helpful in that regard, and it's also helpful to have master's students who are in the two-year programs, you know, so there's some continuity and expertise and, you know, just knowledge about the island and the type of work.
Jane Swanson: That, that we do. So the clubs will form, and they're very busy, the PhD students and the master's students who are the club officers.
Jane Swanson: So we have pretty much set up… a,
Jane Swanson: an engagement process, which is as follows. We will, participate in
Jane Swanson: the Halloween extravaganza on the island, which is a lot of fun, which is the Saturday before Halloween, organized by the governing body on Roosevelt Island, the Roosevelt Island Operating Corporation. We call it REAC.
Jane Swanson: Rosewood Island is unique in that it's on city-owned land, leased to the state.
Jane Swanson: Hmm. Until, you know, 2068, now it's been extended to 20, what, 78? And so there is a governing body that's a little bit different than the rest of
Jane Swanson: most of the rest of New York City, and that is through REAC, and its president is appointed, you know, by the board of… of the REAC board, which is also made up of a number of different folks I won't go into, but happy to tell you about that at some point.
Jane Swanson: So the Halloween Extravaganza is one of their community-wide efforts, they're meaning REAC's community-wide efforts, so the community club does that.
Jane Swanson: There's also a Roosevelt Island Disabled Association on the island, and there are various members of the Community Service Club who help with that. It's every other Friday.
Jane Swanson: And so they do some setup on Thursday before the Friday, food distribution, to the, to the community.
Jane Swanson: Then we offer… 2… One-to-one tech.
Jane Swanson: days for…
Jane Swanson: pretty much older adults on the island, and when I say we, the club, because I'm their advisor, so I'm deeply involved in this. And the one-to-one tech assistance
Jane Swanson: The club gets the students to participate, and I coordinate with the Older Adults Center and another older adults organization on the island.
Jane Swanson: To, get the older adults, and we do a match.
Jane Swanson: You know, they'll tell… older adults will tell me what they need, and then the club will take it and say, you know, who's a good match for this? This person has a Mac, but the student, you know, that signs up may say, oh, I don't use a Mac. So, you know, there'll be a, there'll be a matching.
Jane Swanson: there. So we do that in about November, and then again in February, you know, or March. And those are pretty much the community service club
Jane Swanson: projects. It's, like I said, we… they would like to do more…
Jane Swanson: It's hard for them, because, especially, as you will learn, you know, as you get closer.
Jane Swanson: to, the end of the semester. It's really, really busy, and the same thing with the
Jane Swanson: when you get close to the end of the academic year. Now, you know, we get great feedback
Jane Swanson: the Halloween extravaganza, we don't get any feedback on at all from the community. They love it because we give out candy, you know, what's there to ask? I mean, it's just… we give out a lot of candy, the kids are happy, the parents are happy, everybody's happy. We… we should, and we haven't done,
Jane Swanson: a,
Jane Swanson: How did it go? Or a, you know, a survey, a post-event survey for the one-to-one tech.
Jane Swanson: I haven't done it from… I usually just get rave reviews from…
Jane Swanson: from the older adults, they'll send me a note saying, this was great, or at the event, they'll say, this is the best thing. You know, they're very, very grateful, and we're usually so one-on-one.
Jane Swanson: at this event, that if we can't… if a student can't help an older adult, we kind of figure out why and what they can do. So it's… we kind of know right then
Jane Swanson: by the end of the sessions, how they went. But should we send something? Would it be helpful to have a tool that we would automatically send?
Jane Swanson: Of course. And then, you know what? I think we don't really ask Students!
Jane Swanson: What could be better? What did they learn?
Jane Swanson: What were their learning… were learning outcomes for them? Did this, you know, give them any more awareness of what it's like to do work with an older adult population?
Jane Swanson: So if… if… tool. I think we're all just so, you know, the students are just,
Jane Swanson: So busy that just getting through the event and getting on to the next thing is, you know, really, you know, really the most that they can do.
Jane Swanson: But, you know, I'm retiring at the end of December after having been here for a million years, and what you're helping me with is I'm doing these handover notes to whoever my successor is, and to others here, my supervisor and whatever.
Jane Swanson: So AyU just couldn't have come to me at a better time for me to think about that type of thing.
Jane Swanson: I know that we have, so that's the community service club. The events we…
Jane Swanson: host, I say we, the students host with me as their advisor.
Jane Swanson: The same, you know, I don't know…
Jane Swanson: The food pantry, it's sort of a one-off.
Jane Swanson: Because it's every other Friday. We have the same people know their schedule, and they go.
Jane Swanson: I don't know that it's important to have a tool for how that went.
Jane Swanson: But, definitely, for the one-to-one tech help events, I think
Jane Swanson: And maybe, and particularly on the student side.
Jane Swanson: I mean, after all, they're here to, you know, we're all here to help you all and learn, and…
Jane Swanson: Taking a moment to pause and think about
Jane Swanson: what this experience meant to them. Sometimes.
Jane Swanson: I know one time a student ended up having Thanksgiving.
Jane Swanson: with one of the older adults that they helped. You know, those relation… some of these relationships continue.
Jane Swanson: Over time, and do we track that?
Jane Swanson: No. And we should, to a certain extent.
Jane Swanson: So, that's… are we get… am I getting at the right thing, or…
Jane Swanson: Burke.
Robbie Dornbush: Yes!
Jane Swanson: It's not what you need to know, because I always… I'm always afraid I'm on the wrong track. So you tell me to get on the right track, and I'll get that on the right track.
Robbie Dornbush: Jane, let me tell you, there is no right track. I really appreciate you just, like, detailing all that. I think that was incredibly rich, and, like, really helped us flesh out, the role that you play, as well as, like, the role that your office plays in coordinating community engagement between our institution and other institutions on the island.
Robbie Dornbush: Rachel, do you mind if I, like, ask the next question? Awesome.
Robbie Dornbush: But there's…
Jane Swanson: More, there's more
Jane Swanson: We do. Absolutely. So, but I know we only have 11.30, and I do have kind of a hard stop, at least at 11.35, but I'll be glad to…
Jane Swanson: Tell, you know, to meet with you again, because there's.
Robbie Dornbush: Yeah.
Jane Swanson: very different aspects of what I do. It would help me as well, again, with the handoff notes to my successor. But anyway, go ahead, Robbie.
Robbie Dornbush: Absolutely. One note I would add here, actually, is that both Rachel and I, in addition to just being students here at Cornell Tech, we are also involved in student government, so I'm sure you'll be seeing a lot of us broadly in.
Jane Swanson: Yay! Thank you.
Robbie Dornbush: To me, in regards to that as well. But, you know, pushing, digging deeper, per what you just said, I really appreciate the… you describing the actual activities that you organize, like, and the actions that you do, but, like, looking at an even higher level, how would you characterize your relationship with the other institutions on Roosevelt Island? Like.
Robbie Dornbush: the tenor of your communication with them, like, your… the overall dynamic that you share with these other institutions? How would you describe
Robbie Dornbush: your role. It sounds like you do a lot of convening and bridge building, but I would love to hear a little bit more on that front.
Jane Swanson: We have, you know, we have programs. We have, community conversations with Cornell Tech, where our faculty, you know, talk about what they do, and our postdocs as well. We work with Weill Cornell Medicine on health and wellness seminars. Those are all virtual, where, it's also,
Jane Swanson: co-hosted not only by Cornell Tech, but also by the Roosevelt Island Senior Association. They changed their name to Gloria Good Life on Roosevelt Island Association to include more than just seniors.
Jane Swanson: Anyway, so… and we… I communicate with them. I don't know if you want me to get into the nitty-gritty, but I have a list
Jane Swanson: Help me. Of about 900.
Rachel Liu: Where is your list?
Jane Swanson: where is my list? It's on event, you know, it's, it's… it's just a Google list of… of
Jane Swanson: of everybody that's been in… that I've, sort of.
Jane Swanson: come in contact with on the island, who's expressed an interest, or came to an event, or whatever. And so whenever we have something that we think that they'll be interested in.
Jane Swanson: a program that we're offering for them, or just something they can come to on campus, or also, yes, the one-to-one tech help, I blast out, you know, an email to them. Sometimes, if I think that
Jane Swanson: there's something that I get in my inbox from Cornell University that's a… An event that's…
Jane Swanson: virtual that's being offered, you know, by the mothership, by Ithaca, I'll just say, hey, this looks like it might be interesting for you all. You probably don't know about it, because it, you know, doesn't come to you like it comes to me.
Jane Swanson: And here, you know, you, you know, it's… the public are invited, you know, it's not just for students, or not just for the Ithaca population, it's for anybody that wants to sign on. You know, so it's… it's that. And then.
Jane Swanson: We, we do have relationships with the Roosevelt Island art gallery.
Jane Swanson: The theater, the community theater, the senior center.
Jane Swanson: PSIS217, the school, you know, we have a K-12 program, as you know, which Daria is the, is the new, director of that.
Jane Swanson: We also have a good relationship with Four Freedoms Park. They're, they're,
Jane Swanson: their organization, and I'll have to say, the way of communicating with them, for instance, the 23rd of October.
Jane Swanson: we will have the Student Volunteer Day. You probably know about that. That's not the club, that's what Student and Academic Affairs, you know, puts together for the students, and we go out into the island to all these organizations that I have just mentioned to you.
Jane Swanson: You know, we do that.
Jane Swanson: And to tell you the truth, I mean, there's a… and there's a hospital on the northern tip of the island, Kohler Hospital, that's a long-term care hospital. And just the other night, I was, they have a task force, so I was… the way I communicate with them sometimes is by getting on, you know, that
Jane Swanson: that task force meeting. The Riva Gallery people have events, they have exhibitions all the time, and they have openings on a Saturday night, I swear, once a month, and so I will attend those and talk to people there.
Jane Swanson: The senior center, again, you know, I have such a long-term relationship with that director that we just email each other back and forth. We don't really, you know, hey, you know, we have,
Jane Swanson: We have a group here that, you know, for the summer, of high school students, and they want to do a project, and we bring them into the senior center, and they'll do gardening, or they'll do one-to-one tech, or something like that.
Jane Swanson: And, you know, we will post, for instance, the Main Street theater and Dance. They want to get our students up to their events. The same with the gallery. They want to get our students up to their events.
Jane Swanson: So they have flyers, and we try, try, try to include those in the student newsletter and on the e-boards, you know, in the house. But that's a challenge, because the main… and I'm going off, I know I am… The main,
Jane Swanson: One of the main prob… one of the main problems that I have
Jane Swanson: in terms of tools and measuring, is people say, your students never come up past the subway, and we want them to come and go to the restaurants, and visit the gallery, and go to the theater, and now there's a thrift shop, and it's good. Shop at the thrift shop.
Jane Swanson: Yeah, isn't it cool? Yeah, yeah, it's cool. Yeah, the person who run… Edin, you'll meet Edin, because she is, the PhD student who runs, really, the community service club, even though she's PhD. She and Daniel. And,
Jane Swanson: you know, it's her favorite place, she's there every day. But we… we don't have a… I mean, how can you measure? They're, like, putting a bracelet on every student that.
Rachel Liu: Yes.
Jane Swanson: How often they go up. See, you were just there.
Jane Swanson: But yet, the community, and, you know, the vocal part, there's always that. The community will say, you know, Jane, the people, the students never come up here, you know. And you do, Rachel, you were at
Jane Swanson: You know, at the thrift shop. So that is,
Jane Swanson: That has been a problem that
Jane Swanson: Sticks in the mind of older adults who… have this… impression.
Jane Swanson: That our students…
Jane Swanson: stay on campus. There's a little bit of truth to that, you know, because the subway's right there, and the…
Jane Swanson: trams right there, and then, you know, you go… they're exploring the city, and do they explore all the way… all the way north? So, we used to have the Student Volunteer Day in the spring, which was kind of stupid, except it was the best time for the students.
Jane Swanson: Because… and now we moved it to the fall, so they can get to know, you know, we try to point out when we go to our events for, you know, our volunteer organizations, for them to…
Jane Swanson: get to know the town a little bit, as well as get to know each other, you know, early on in the program, because they go in groups of 4 or 5, you know, to each of the… you'll say, to each of the organizations. So it is a little bit… you can… I think you can see or tell or hear my frustration of…
Jane Swanson: I'm not a systems
Jane Swanson: per… and it's just me. You know, I don't have… I have… I share an admin with, you know, a bunch of other people.
Jane Swanson: But I don't have anybody… I don't have a staff. It's just always been me. So… and I'm not the best at keeping records to begin with. Boy, can I tell this when I do my handover notes. I'm trying to make a good system for me, for my successor, whoever that might be, to know, you know, to not just come in and go, what do they do here?
Jane Swanson: I'm still not answering this, I don't think, quite.
Jane Swanson: Right, but it's through my relationships, and sort of the, you know, the stopping in to see folks, emailing, going to their events.
Jane Swanson: you know, where I just sort of maintain these relationships, reminding them to send their flyers to events so we can post things.
Jane Swanson: On them.
Jane Swanson: Do you want to hear about REAC, my relationship with them, the governing body, or… I'm just gonna shut up, you can ask me a bunch of questions.
Robbie Dornbush: I have one quick question, actually, just, like, a very quick follow-up. How long do you think it took you to build these relationships?
Jane Swanson: I know, that's what everybody's worried about here, because I took… I've been here since 2014.
Jane Swanson: Oh, here's an important thing I should tell you, and this is… well, it's not… it's just important to me, probably, but when we used to have space in Google, you know, at the Google building, until our campus… the Googlers gave us free space, so when I started in 2014,
Jane Swanson: You know, we weren't built out here until 2017, so we've been here 10 years come next year. And, our campus. And…
Jane Swanson: You know, leadership at the time had a great idea, I wish it was mine. I went over and sat in the gallery.
Jane Swanson: the art gallery, Wednesdays and Fridays, from 10 to 4.
Jane Swanson: And we had renderings.
Jane Swanson: On these stanchions of our… of our campus.
Jane Swanson: Because… and then in the window, the gallery could be open.
Jane Swanson: the hours that I was there, so I played art gallery director, you know, for that
Jane Swanson: time. People could come in, so I would meet people that way.
Jane Swanson: I, you know, met a lot of people. I knew a lot of people, because I had worked for elected officials who represented Roosevelt Island, and I already had those. That's why I was hired, so I already had some of those relationships. And that makes this job unusual, and why people are kind of afraid of, oh my god, how do we…
Jane Swanson: replicate me, not so much because I'm wonderful, but because before I came here, I worked for a city council member whose district included Roosevelt Island, so I had some of these contacts.
Jane Swanson: You know, that's not going to be the case for anybody that comes in to this… comes into this job.
Jane Swanson: But being in that gallery, and that, you know, and we paid the gallery rent, a little bit of rent, so they got a little bit of rent. They got me to have the place open for those two days, and I got the benefit of having people come in
Jane Swanson: And then that warm relationship sort of developed, you know, with some of these folks. With some of these folks then.
Jane Swanson: I didn't… now I can't even remember your question.
Robbie Dornbush: And just, like, a quick rephrasing, it sounds like you, over time, just really built these relationships,
Jane Swanson: Yeah.
Robbie Dornbush: Quite frankly, the old-fashioned way, like, you just started meeting people, you've started talking with them, like, they're, like, in a very, like, human way, you, like, met and, like, really fostered these, relationships that have led to success and, like, led to all the things that we do today.
Jane Swanson: It's true, and I don't know,
Jane Swanson: whoever my successor is will have the advantage of the mailing list, right, of the… of the email list. And the email list is just so-so to begin with. I mean, there are a lot of… there are a lot of… they're not all Roosevelt Islanders. There's people we've met along the way, and we, you know, it's community relations, not just for Roosevelt Island.
Jane Swanson: But a large, you know, great deal of it is.
Jane Swanson: But I would say, you know, when I maybe meet with my successor, it'd be… it really is, you know, the,
Jane Swanson: it really is walk… you know, walking around. I mean, and is this… this is probably a little bit different for… this is unique, right? Because it's… although…
Jane Swanson: New York City's a ser… you know, is a city of neighborhoods, so, you know, no matter what you're doing, you know, you're gonna… you're still gonna need that, pounding the pavement, going into organizations, meeting with them one-on-one, trying to find out how can we partner with you, what are your…
Jane Swanson: folks need, and how can we, you know… and I'll tell you, you probably learned, if you went to the round robin that Edin did, because I couldn't come.
Jane Swanson: At the round robin, where we all go through what we do, we…
Jane Swanson: I call this, what I always say, what Roosevelt Islanders can do for you and what you can do for Roosevelt Islanders. Because I already have, you know, students coming to me saying, can you connect me with the Senior Center for my project? Can you connect me with the art gallery? Or, you know, we're doing this
Jane Swanson: You know, like you are doing, you know, we're doing this, you know, working on this product or service in studio, product studio, and we need to talk to community people, and they love it so very much.
Jane Swanson: Yeah.
Jane Swanson: Have you talked to Needy Parique? Is she on your list?
Rachel Liu: No, but she's a… I work at the Maker Lab as well, so I'm definitely gonna chat with her about that. And then I would love…
Jane Swanson: Nobody better for community than UT.
Rachel Liu: That's really good to know. And then for Eden, or Edin, I would love to…
Jane Swanson: It's… think Ed, Edward, but.
Rachel Liu: Okay, Edin, I see, I see. Do you have her contact information?
Jane Swanson: I can email that to you. Okay, perfect.
Rachel Liu: Yeah, that'd be…
Jane Swanson: And she lives in the Octagon at the north… does she live in the Octagon? Yeah.
Jane Swanson: And this… she has found her community.
Jane Swanson: Wow. I mean, this is her… she is heavily involved with the Roosevelt Island Historical Association, Judy Birdie, the unofficial mayor of Roosevelt Island, who…
Jane Swanson: I love, that drives us crazy. And she belongs to the synagogue. She has found her community. She is so happy here.
Jane Swanson: And when you talk to Edin.
Jane Swanson: you will learn so much more than you're learning from me. She has such a unique perspective on the island and community engagement and…
Jane Swanson: is in, you know, just part of her blood. I mean, she… it's… she's so good. You need to talk to Ed, and I can probably more than help you myself, I can put you in touch with… but folks like that. Niti, oh my gosh.
Jane Swanson: She knows how to weave in community and intergenerational in her classes.
Jane Swanson: And that's pretty special.
Jane Swanson: Okay, good.
Rachel Liu: This has been super helpful. I know you've got a hard stop.
Jane Swanson: 35, I can… I can… I can… I'm just going over to help Tanya in the reuse center, so I told her I could be a few.
Rachel Liu: Okay.
Rachel Liu: Awesome. I guess, Robbie, do you mind if I ask the final question?
Robbie Dornbush: Absolutely.
Rachel Liu: Okay, perfect. I would love to know your, like, blue sky, ideal experience from not just, like, communicating, like, in your current job right now with, like, your, the community members, but also
Rachel Liu: Even maybe sharing a little bit about what you hope, the turnover process would look like when the new person comes in, like, how the information gets transferred, and hopefully,
Rachel Liu: Maybe, like, what you hoped that they would be able to take, from your… from your experience.
Jane Swanson: You know,
Jane Swanson: I think it might be a little bit the old-fashioned way, but, you know, you're trying to think of something that would help me. I think these handover notes
Jane Swanson: You know, that I could organize in a fashion so that
Jane Swanson: God forbid if I were hit by a bus tomorrow, you know, they would say, but yeah, I know, sorry, Rob, that's awful, I shouldn't have said that.
Jane Swanson: That, you know, you know what I mean, that, that they could take right over. There is this woman, oh my god, Diane Levitt ran our K-12 program for, a million years, like, like me, and her handover notes…
Jane Swanson: To her successor?
Jane Swanson: Wow.
Jane Swanson: She has a link To every single one of her… Team meeting notes.
Rachel Liu: Whoa.
Jane Swanson: From the day she started, almost, maybe not quite that, but you know what.
Jane Swanson: Yeah.
Jane Swanson: And the links to all of, collaborators.
Jane Swanson: important people, and that's what… that's what I have to do. Is put together this document.
Jane Swanson: That'll indicate who our… who our partners are on the island, in government, in, you know, on… RIOC on the island.
Jane Swanson: who our partners are at Cornell University.
Jane Swanson: you know, at city agencies. How did we work or not work well with and coordinate? This is another thing, and I'm not sure…
Jane Swanson: You're getting into this or not.
Jane Swanson: But I think, like all big organizations, this place is pretty siloed, so that you'll have somebody doing government affairs, me.
Jane Swanson: But yet, a faculty member knows somebody in city government… in the… in the DOE, you know, and has a connection there, and all of a sudden, this program will grow, and you're going, what the heck?
Jane Swanson: I have no idea, you know, what this is. That's happened, like, a lot. And a lot of that's on me in terms of…
Jane Swanson: But, you know, faculty understand they do what they want to, but they're still good. There's some staff, you know, people that head up the urban tech program and the public interest tech program.
Jane Swanson: that I think… In this role of mine, To have folks integrated more.
Jane Swanson: Like, if there was some tool…
Jane Swanson: Government relations. Government and community relations.
Jane Swanson: where everybody would have access to what they're doing and know to add to that document, hi, I just met with blah blah blah, and we might do a program with them. You know, just…
Jane Swanson: That's my pie in the sky.
Jane Swanson: You know, if you had… and maybe that's not what you want, but that's what I need. That's what we need. We need somewhere, and I know there probably is, you know, you… there probably is that I just haven't used it, or we're not all using it, or we don't know how to be regular and, you know, systematic about it.
Jane Swanson: Oh my god, I'm going off on a tangent.
Rachel Liu: This is super helpful, Jane.
Jane Swanson: It's making me crazy.
Rachel Liu: We are… I mean, hopefully, like.
Jane Swanson: Are you gonna… is this gonna… you're gonna show this to Josh or somebody? Because Josh is gonna… okay.
Robbie Dornbush: Where, where's.
Rachel Liu: We're gonna have these notes, we're gonna share them to you if it's helpful for your turnover.
Jane Swanson: I'm never going… yes. I probably will.
Rachel Liu: But I'm not…
Jane Swanson: I'm gonna look at the video.
Rachel Liu: Yes.
Jane Swanson: supposed to start Zoom AI? Oh.
Rachel Liu: This would… this… I mean, we're really just using this to see if we missed anything in our notes, but Robbie.
Jane Swanson: Oh, I know what you mean.
Rachel Liu: out-takers I've ever seen. He's just…
Jane Swanson: Oh, note taker?
Robbie Dornbush: Yes, I am.
Rachel Liu: Incredible note-taker.
Robbie Dornbush: What are your programs?
Jane Swanson: programs? What are you… you guys gotta go, but what are you ma… what is your program? I'm so sorry I didn't ask a thing about you, and you're asking all about me.
Robbie Dornbush: No worries.
Rachel Liu: We will be, we'll be hanging out, Jane, like, we both won't.
Jane Swanson: the student government.
Rachel Liu: And definitely, yeah.
Jane Swanson: Enraged me, yeah.
Jane Swanson: Yeah.
Rachel Liu: But I'm Ori, I'm Operations Research.
Jane Swanson: Ori, okay, and Robbie.
Robbie Dornbush: And I'm a one-year MBA, so… Oh!
Jane Swanson: I know, I wish you were both 2 years. I know. Except I'll be gone, and I forgot about that.
Rachel Liu: We both lived in the city for, like, quite a few years already, so…
Jane Swanson: Any of you.
Rachel Liu: I'm planning on staying here, at least for me.
Jane Swanson: Oh, God.
Robbie Dornbush: in here.
Rachel Liu: a while.
Robbie Dornbush: Yeah.
Rachel Liu: That's good, that's good. Yes.
Jane Swanson: Good.
Rachel Liu: But anyways, thank you so much, Jane.
Jane Swanson: Thank you for being… for doing this.
Rachel Liu: If you, if you could send.
Jane Swanson: Anything.
Rachel Liu: Aiden's email, that would be really helpful.
Jane Swanson: I'm gonna do that right now.
Rachel Liu: to… to Nidia as well, but thank you so.
Jane Swanson: Yeah, you're very welcome. I'm gonna send that right now.
Jane Swanson: All right.
Robbie Dornbush: Awesome.
Jane Swanson: Okay. Thank you.
Robbie Dornbush: Thank you.
Jane Swanson: Have a great day.
Robbie Dornbush: It is.
Jane Swanson: Appreciated by…
Robbie Dornbush: late.